Do you want subtitles for any video?
-=[ ai.OpenSubtitles.com ]=-
We are now closer
than we've ever been.
We are now closer than
we have ever been to victory.
Some...
Some are already calling it
the greatest...
the greatest victory
in the history of mankind.
Some are calling it already...
We are closer than
we have ever been to victory.
Some are already calling it
the greatest victory
in the history of military campaigns.
Today. I can announce
that the so-called Western Forces
of Texas and California
have suffered a very great loss.
A very great defeat
at the hands of the fighting men and
women of the United States military.
The people of Texas and California
should know that they will be
welcomed back to these United States
as soon as their illegal
secessionist government is deposed.
I can also confirm
that the Florida alliance
has failed in its attempt
to force the brave people
of the Carolinas
into joining the insurrection.
Citizens of America
we are now closer than ever
to a historic victory
as we eliminate
the final pockets of resistance.
God bless you all
and God Bless America.
Give us some water...!
I've been waiting two hours.
Stand back. Hey. just back up.
We want water!
I have a baby.
Lee.
You all right?
Help!
Here...
You okay?
I'm fine.
- What?
You're Lee Smith?
This is crazy.
- Take this.
- No. I can't take that from you.
Take it and put it on.
Thank you so much.
- Run!
- Oh. shit.
We woke up in Des Moines. Iowa.
And he's wearing my wedding ring.
Yeah!
Jesus. The Wi-Fi is fucking slow.
The word I'm getting it's July 4th.
The word you're getting.
Like everyone in this room
hasn't already heard his bullshit.
July 4th. Sam.
The optics are irresistible.
The Western Forces are stopped
120 miles from D.C.
The Florida Alliance
aren't far south of that.
The WF wasn't stopped. They stalled.
They lost their supply lines.
But it's the race Berlin.
There's no coordination
between the Secessionists.
You watch.
Soon as D.C. falls.
they'll turn on each other.
Really?
It's every night this week.
They'll switch to the generator.
Upload was almost done.
So. where you kids headed tomorrow?
Staying in New York a while
or venturing out?
Fuck you.
Come on. Joe.
So you can beat us there?
I couldn't beat you in a brisk walk.
We're going to D.C.. Sammy.
Tomorrow morning. first thing.
- Yeah. front line. I figured.
- No.
No. not the frontline.
D.C.
What?
I'm gonna photograph the President.
Joe's gonna interview.
Photograph and
interview the President?
In D.C.?
That's the idea.
What the fuck are you talking about?
Are you serious?
They shoot journalists on sight
in the capital.
They literally see us
as enemy combatants.
Not a single interview in 14 months.
And how are you gonna do this?
We get there before anyone else does.
You think there's a rush
to get executed on the South Lawn?
Sammy. July 4th. July 10th.
West Coast Forces.
fucking Portland Maoists
it's all the same.
D.C. is falling
and the President is dead
inside a month.
Interviewing him
is the only story left.
It's not a story
if it never gets filed.
Lee. can I please
talk you out of this bullshit?
What do you think
the route's gonna be like?
There's nothing direct.
The interstates have vaporized. And
you can't get anywhere near Philly.
So you gotta go west.
maybe as far as Pittsburgh
then circle in from West Virginia.
You already had that route
all figured out. huh. Sammy?
Yeah. okay. I was kind of
looking to get down there myself.
- Knew it.
- Not D.C.
I don't want
a piece of your suicide pact.
I want Charlottsville.
the front line.
- Sam.
- Hear me out.
Just 'cause
I'm a rival news outlet...
You're not a fucking rival.
You think I care if you fight
with whatever's left
of The New York Times?
You're worried I'm too old.
Can't move quick enough.
Aren't you?
Sure.
Yes.
But...
you're gonna make me explain
why I have to be there?
If it's the front line you want
half the press in this room are gonna
be heading there within 24 hours.
You want me to walk around
this fucking room begging for a ride?
I'm gonna finish the upload
upstairs and pass out.
Hopefully it'll be done
by the time I wake up.
My vote.
If Sammy wants a ride.
I'm good with it.
You two figure it out.
Thank you. Lee.
Yeah. thank you. Lee.
Make me the bad guy.
Ma'am. just a warning.
If you take the elevator.
we do sometimes have power cuts
which might mean
a delay in your journey.
A delay?
We offer the option
to use the stairs.
I'm on the tenth floor.
Your choice. ma'am.
Miss Smith?
Hey. it's me.
Do you remember me from earlier?
Yeah. How did you know I was...
Yeah. I didn't mean
to. like. stalk. but
I know a lot of the press
use this hotel.
And I wanted to say thanks.
And I want to give you this back.
Oh. no. It's okay. keep it.
- But I'm sure...
- Keep it. And
buy a helmet
and some Kevlar. okay?
If you're planning on
attending more stuff like that.
I am. yeah. going to.
I'm a photographer and I wanna be
a war photographer actually.
By the way. you have
the same name as my hero.
Lee Miller.
She was one of the first
photojournalists into Dachau.
Do you know her stuff?
Yeah. I know who Lee Miller is.
Of course.
But I want to say that
you're also one of my heroes.
And you've got the same name too.
Wow.
Thank you. I'm in good company.
What's your name?
Jessie.
Jessie Cullen.
So. Jessie. I've gotta walk up
ten flights of stairs.
But. if I ever see you again
you better be wearing Kevlar
and that fluorescent.
You bet.
A word?
What the fuck
is that girl doing here?
Right. So. she came over
to the table last night
after you went to bed
and we got talking and...
she's very cool.
And wanted to tag along.
So. she's coming with us?
Lee. you let Sammy tag along.
You think he's gonna do well
running for cover
with bullets flying over his head?
She's a kid. did you notice that?
She's. like. 23
and she wants to do what we do.
She wants to do what you do.
We had to start one day.
Were you much older than she is now?
Whatever happens. she goes
no further than Charlottesville.
All right. Let's go.
You don't wanna miss this.
Mr. President. do you regret
any actions implemented
during your third term in office?
I'm not gonna softball him. Sammy.
In retrospect. Mr. President
do you still think
it was wise to disband the FBI?
Passive aggressive.
Sir. how is your policy evolving
in the use of air strikes
against American citizens?
Yeah. Now we're talking.
Just be sure you get the words out
before the piano wire gets too tight.
There's a gas station up ahead.
Looks open.
We've got over half a tank.
What do you think?
Any chance to refuel. we should take.
Okay.
Help you. folks?
Just looking for gas.
Got a local fuel permit?
No. we're... we're actually
just passing through.
Can't help. sorry.
Sir. if we pay?
I was never gonna give it for free.
Over the odds.
What's over the odds?
300.
For half a tank and two cans.
300 buys you a sandwich.
We got ham or cheese.
300 Canadian.
Okay.
Hey.
Stretching your legs?
No. I just saw
something from the road.
This isn't going to take long.
Sure.
Are we good?
Yeah. we're good.
Go ahead. check it out. Come on.
I told her...
I don't mind if she looks.
Who are they?
Looters.
I got kids. man.
I actually know that guy.
Went to high school together.
He didn't talk to me much.
Much more talkative now.
We've been debating what to do
with them for two days now.
Been going around in circles.
Tell you what.
Why don't you put us and them
out of our misery? Make the call.
I'll put rounds in them right now.
Or beat 'em up a little more.
Strap them to the front.
We'll let them go
after a couple of days.
Flip a coin if you like.
Would you stand with them?
- Stand with them?
- Yeah.
I'd like to take your picture.
Okay.
Just stand over there?
Yeah.
Where do you want me?
Between the two.
Gotcha.
I didn't take a photo.
I didn't take a single photo.
I didn't even remember
I had cameras on me.
Like. oh. my God. like...
like. why didn't I just tell him
not to shoot them?
They were probably gonna
kill them anyway.
- How do you know?
- He doesn't know
but that's besides the point.
Once you start asking yourself
those questions. you can't stop.
So we don't ask.
We record. so other people ask.
You wanna be a journalist?
That's the job.
- Hey. Lee.
- What?
Back off.
What am I saying that's wrong?
I'm not saying it's wrong.
she's just shook up.
Lee doesn't understand "shook up".
I'm not being protective of her?
You're the idiot
who let her in this car.
What happened back there
is nothing in comparison
to what we're heading into.
You need to understand...
Holy shit. she's crying.
The back seat is both kindergarten
and an old people's home.
How did this happen?
Lee. what the fuck?
Lee's right.
I won't make that mistake again.
The terms of
the so-called Peace Summit
could only be rejected.
fully rejected
by all right-thinking Americans.
To the secessionists.
I say only this.
I pledge allegiance to the flag
of the United States of America.
We stand ready to fulfill
the promise of our forefathers
to the flag. to the nation
and to God.
Stop here a minute.
Seem like a good place
for a toilet break?
Just pull in.
Come with me.
Shoot it.
- Shoot the helicopter?
- Yeah.
It's gonna make a good image.
FE2s.
You don't see them around much.
Yeah.
They were my dad's cameras actually.
Don't worry. he's not dead. He's...
sitting on his farm in Missouri
pretending like
none of this is happening.
Lee
I'm sorry for jamming my way
into your ride. okay?
I know you're really angry about it
and I know you think
I don't know shit. but...
I'm not angry about that. Jesse.
I don't care what you do
or don't know.
Okay. but you are angry with me.
There is no version of this
that isn't a mistake.
I know. because I'm it.
Joe and Sammy are it.
- It's my choice.
- Right.
And I'll remember that
when you lose your shit.
or you get blown up or shot.
Would you photograph that moment
if I got shot?
What do you think?
Every time I survived a war zone
and got the photo
I thought I was sending
a warning home.
"Don't do this."
But here we are.
So it's existential.
What is?
What's eating you.
Don't worry about me. Sammy.
Am I allowed to say
I remember you at her age?
And I wasn't so different?
You weren't so different.
You think you're being hard on her
and I think
you're being hard on yourself.
Okay. writer.
Damn it. Lee.
Stop.
I'm speaking truth.
And for the record. sure.
I'm worried about that girl.
And I'm worried about you too.
What are you worrying about Lee for?
Lee's lost her faith
in the power of journalism.
State of the nation is QED.
I can't answer to that. Sammy.
But I can tell you
this gunfire
is getting me extremely fucking hard.
Look at that shit light up the sky.
It's not our story.
Yeah.
But you know. bang bang.
We're not going anywhere near that
in the dark.
But sun up.
If they're still at it.
we'll take a look.
Cool.
Thanks.
Action tomorrow.
We're going down there?
Yeah.
But not you.
You're gonna...
You're gonna hang back.
I don't wanna hang back.
You'll have to hang back.
I'm not hanging back.
You should see your face.
Stomach doing turns. Right?
You won't get
a minute of sleep tonight.
My advice
don't expect to sleep.
That way if you do. it's a...
it's a nice surprise.
You're gonna sleep?
I got out-of-date Ativan.
Got plenty.
I can give you some if you like.
Oh. no. It's okay.
Or I can stay up with you.
Keep you company.
No. I...
I don't wanna be
a burden or whatever.
You sure?
But seriously
if you do get freaked out
or something. just wake me up.
It's not nice being scared alone.
Thanks. Joe.
You bet. darlin'.
Get down!
I said go flank the building!
- Alright. Mike!
- Fuck!
Mike. come on!
Get me the fuck out of here!
I said go flank the fucking building!
Got it.
Do something!
- If I run now.
- Get ready to move.
- I'm gonna get hit! Get me
- Prep the smoke.
- The fuck out of here!
- Okay!
- Fuck!
- Smoke out!
On the count of three.
Three. two. one.
- Go!
- Cover me!
- Fuck!
- Mike's down.
- Shit!
- I'm gonna get him!
- Go get him!
Now! Now. move it!
You gotta move!
Mike's down! We gotta get him!
Mike's down. I'm gonna get him.
Move back!
I gotcha. hang in. Stay with me.
Fuck. get me gauze.
Fuck it!
No.
Holy fucking shit!
What a fucking rush!
- You're press?
- Yes. ma'am.
IDs.
Okay. Are you staying the night?
Yeah. just one.
Park over there.
There's a canteen where you can eat.
And no tents available.
Thanks. ma'am.
You're good.
- Hey. get in there.
- I'm gonna show these kids.
- Yeah.
- Check this out. Okay!
- One. two three. four...
- 11. 12. 13...
Can I go next?
Your turn. Sammy.
Hey. wait up!
Brought you something.
Thanks.
Don't forget to eat.
Yeah. I'm starving.
I'll eat once I'm done with this.
Developing negs on the road.
Yeah. I got myself
a pretty neat travel kit.
I'm impressed.
Want to know the secret of
getting the developer just right?
Body temperature.
- Smart.
- Thank you.
So. how about
you tell me the story of
how you became a photo journalist?
You don't know?
Thought I was one of your heroes.
Yeah. I do.
When you were in college
you took the motherfucking legendary
photo of the ANTIFA massacre.
And then you became the youngest
ever Magnum photographer.
That would be my Wikipedia page.
But what's missing from it?
I don't know. A lot.
Well. that's gotta sit here
for ten minutes
so you might as well expand a little.
What about your folks?
Well. actually.
they're on a farm too.
Except Colorado.
Also pretending this isn't happening.
No shit.
Hey. these are dry.
Should we check them out?
Sure.
Still need a phone even though
you can't get a signal.
I don't want you to see these.
They're not even in focus. Like...
Exposure all wrong.
Just keep looking.
I figure the strike rate
for keepers is 30 to one.
It's a great photo. Jessie.
Did we just drive through
a time portal?
It's The Twilight Zone.
Hey there. Welcome.
Feel free to look around.
Hey.
Out of interest
are you guys aware there's like a...
pretty huge civil war
going on all across America?
Sure. but we just try to stay out.
Stay out?
With what we see on the news.
seems like it's for the best.
Yeah.
Well. let me know
if you want to try anything on.
Thanks.
Lee.
What?
You're so war-torn
you can't try on a dress?
Jesus.
When you haven't seen
yourself in the mirror...
- Oh. my God. Shut the fuck up.
- In a few days.
Turn around.
I want to take your photo.
No.
It's... Come on.
Yes.
Are you gonna take the photo?
Told me not to rush.
Yeah. but there's a sweet spot.
and you're missing it.
Don't wanna miss your sweet spot.
Well. no. that was not the moment.
Okay.
One more.
- Lee?
- Yes.
You're pretty when you smile.
There you go.
Hey.
How about this?
Yeah. nice.
You're not gonna take a picture?
Right.
You know what. though?
Running a little low on film.
You're mean.
I'm out.
I'm gonna go try this on.
You actually bought something?
She did.
She's paying now.
It's so weird.
This place is like
everything I'd forgotten.
Funny.
I was thinking it felt like
everything I remembered.
Look at the tops of the buildings.
Be subtle.
Wouldn't have suited us anyway. Lee.
We'd have gotten bored.
I remain ready to accept
the full. immediate and unconditional
surrender of the Secessionist forces.
To deliberate the people
of the subjugated states
and start rebuilding
our great nation.
- I've had enough of this shit.
- The land of the free...
Words might as well be random.
What do you think he'll actually say
if I do get a mic in front of him?
Not much.
The ones that get taken.
Qaddafi. Mussolini. Ceauşescu
they're always lesser men
than you think.
At the end. he'll let you down. Joe.
Just as long as he isn't dead
before I get there.
Hold up.
There was a turn off
three or four miles back.
Maybe we should turn around.
take another route.
Can you see anything?
No.
Nothing. no shapes.
no movement. nothing?
No.
Okay. I'm gonna
drive forward a little.
Should I keep going?
Shit!
Where you going?
- With them.
- Don't be such a hotshot.
Just keep your head down.
No shit.
I wouldn't try driving on.
This guy's a good shot.
Hey.
What's going on?
Someone in that house.
They're stuck.
We're stuck.
Who do you think they are?
No idea.
Hey.
We're press.
Cool.
Now I understand why it's written
on the side of your vehicle.
Are you WF? Who's givin' you orders?
No one's giving us orders. man.
Someone's trying to kill us.
We're trying to kill them.
You don't know
what side they're fighting for?
I get it.
You're retarded.
You don't understand a word I say.
Yo.
What's over there in that house?
Someone shooting.
Guys.
Shut the fuck up.
I got good news.
Why don't you put
your head down then?
Thank you. Sammy. I'm good.
Take it from an old hand.
Sleep any chance you get.
You never know what's coming
around the next corner.
Yeah. all right.
- Sammy.
- What?
Got a car comin' up on us
pretty fast.
What do you think?
I don't know.
Maybe they're just in a hurry.
They're in a hurry. all right.
He smoked his tyres
on the last corner.
Okay.
Well. we're not gonna
outrun anyone in this thing.
So. slow down a little. Lee.
Let 'em pass.
Roger that.
Don't look out at 'em.
They just roll on by.
Oh. shit. Here we go.
What the fuck?
Tony?
- Fuck you!
- What the fuck!
How are you guys doing?
You just scared the shit out of me.
Good! That was the idea!
What the fuck are you doing here?
I don't know. Joe.
What are you doing here?
Fuck you!
God. small world.
Small world. my ass.
They were following us.
Did you tell them where
we were headed back in New York?
Fuck no.
Hey. Tony.
Did Joe tell you where we were going
back in New York?
I don't know. Lee.
He was pretty drunk
when he was hitting on that girl
you got on the back seat.
- Oh. God.
- You're a dick.
Look. I must've been so wasted.
Lee. I'm done with Bohai.
He's lousy company
and he drives like a maniac!
(Chinese) What did you just say?
(Chinese)
You drive like a grandmother.
Dude. what are you doing?
I come over to your car!
- Tony!
- Dude!
Are you fucking crazy. Tony?
- Just keep the car steady. Lee!
- No! Fuck!
Don't worry. I've done this before.
- Steady the car!
- What the fuck!
Just keep the car steady. Lee.
(Chinese) Closer...!
Give me a hand.
You're out of your fucking mind.
- You crazy bastard!
- That was so cool!
So fucking sick!
I gotta do it.
What?
I'm doing it.
Jesus. Lee.
Don't turn the wheel.
My new passenger. Much better...
- Bye-bye!
- Pull over.
Bye bye. Tony. Bye bye.
See you in Washington.
Fuck you!
I told you he drives like a maniac.
Where did they go?
This feel funny?
Where'd your guy go. Tony?
He's just fucking around. that's all.
I don't want him fuckin' around.
I want Jessie back in this car.
Relax. Lee. He's just showing
how fast he can drive.
The girl's fine.
How the fuck do you know
if she's fine? Can you see her?
Fuck!
Oh. fuck.
Shit.
We need to go down there. Now.
If we go down there.
they're going to kill us.
No.
Those aren't government forces.
Not out here.
We got our press passes. We're cool.
Those people do not want to be seen
doing what they're doing.
Tell us. Lee.
They're talking.
They're probably just
giving them a scare.
They killed all the people
in that fucking truck.
They could've killed the whole town.
but they will stop now?
Who knows
where those bodies are from?
Are the bodies in uniform?
No. they're not.
I'm going down.
- I'm coming with you.
- Me too.
I'm telling you every instinct in me
says this is death. okay? Death.
You stay. You stay
'cause you're old and you can't run.
Fuck it.
Shit.
Fuck this.
- Who's doing the talking?
- Me.
Okay.
Wyatt. there's one hung up in there.
Hey!
Hey. guys.
What's happening?
Guess there's...
there's some kind of
misunderstanding here.
Yeah?
Yes. sir.
Those two guys over there.
they're my colleagues.
What kind of colleagues?
Journalists. sir.
We're actually just...
We're passing through.
Passing through to where?
Charlottsville.
Charlottsville?
What's in Charlottsville?
Good hiking.
I hear.
Actually. we are...
No. we're covering
the university campus there.
They started the new program.
They are re-opening the school
which is a surreal feel-good story.
And I guess we all need that. Right?
Yeah.
- This guy is your colleague?
- Yes.
- This guy here?
- Yes. sir. He's my...
That guy?
Sir.
Just...
Just what?
- Just what? This...
- You know what? What?
- Just. please... Let's just...
- Just. please?
- Sir. please.
- Please. sir.
- Yes. speak.
- Just let me...
We're American journalists.
You told me that already.
Okay. we...
We work for Reuters.
Reuters doesn't sound American.
It's a news agency.
- I know what Reuters is.
- Sir. Okay.
- I'm just saying...
- Just saying. just what?
We're American. okay?
Okay. What kind of American are you?
Central American. South American?
What?
Florida.
Florida?
Central?
What about you? Where are you from?
Tell him. Jessie.
Missouri.
Missouri?
The "show-me" state. right?
- Yes.
- You know what they call it?
Yes.
Why do they call it
the "show-me" state?
I don't know.
You don't know?
It's American.
It is American. 100%.
What about you? Where are you from?
Colorado.
Colorado. Missouri.
That's what I'm talking about.
American.
Who is this guy hiding over here?
Hey. Buddy.
What's your deal? Where are you from?
Huh?
Where are you from?
What? You can't speak? Are you mute?
You can't speak English?
Yes. you can? Yes. you can.
Okay.
When you open your mouth
and tell me where you're from
just make sure
it's clear fucking English. Okay?
Where are you from?
I'm from... I'm from Hong Kong.
China.
Sir. just...
- No!
- What?
- Just stop it. okay?
- Stop?
No...!
- Who the fuck
- Just stop it!
- Do you think you are?
- Stop! Please!
Get in the car!
Get in the fucking car!
Go...!
Go!
We gotta stop.
What are you talking about?
I can't drive.
We can't stop.
You gotta fucking drive.
- Joe.
- I can't.
He's been hit. He's bleeding.
No...
Fuck!
Fuck.
Okay. get out. Get out.
Let's go.
Come on. Let's go. Sammy.
- Okay...
- Come on.
Fuck!
We just heard about Sammy.
And the other two guys.
Tony. Bohai. Their names.
Lee. I'm really sorry.
I know what he was to you.
It's so fucked up.
Oh. it's so fucked up.
Now you wait until you hear
what these two embattled
motherfuckers have to say.
Joe. I'm just trying
to talk to Lee about Sammy.
I know. Yeah. I heard
your condolences. Means a lot.
Now just... just tell her.
We loved Sammy. everyone did.
Thank you. Anya.
Fuck. The Western Forces
are moving to D.C.
Earlier today. the Government
military basically surrendered.
Yeah. that's true.
D.C.'s only protection now.
Few do-or-die soldiers.
handful of secret service.
WF's gonna roll right in.
So. you and I. we're too late.
We missed the story.
And Sammy didn't even die
for anything good.
Where's Joe?
Processing.
Me. too.
Hardly knew Sammy
compared to you. but...
Yeah. you knew him.
The man you were with.
that's who he was.
It may sound fucked up
but there are so many ways
that it could've ended for him.
And a lot of them were worse.
He didn't wanna quit.
These last few days
I've never been scared
like that before.
And I've never felt more alive.
- Stand back!
- Hold!
We got a sniper!
Man down!
Let's go...!
Move...!
Take your positions! Move...!
Move. on me!
Turn...!
Lee?
Let's go!
- Move...!
- Come on...!
We got 'em...!
Go...!
Get to the blocking position now!
- Fire!
- Incoming!
Fucks sake! Stay down!
Friendlies...
Move it up. move it up!
Lock it down!
Hey. we're here to help.
What do you need?
We got two over there
and two in the tower.
I can send a main round
right through that tower.
- Yeah. just fucking do it. do it.
- Check.
Shipwreck! On me! Drop that bitch!
Stand back!
Ladies. get your heads down
and tuck in.
Gun tower on the north side
of 17th street. Mark my tracer.
Go...!
Move...!
Let's go...!
This way!
Lee. you gotta move. okay?
We have to move. Let's go...!
Now!
Down! Get down...!
Hey. blow the gate! Push it back...!
- Get back.
- Roger that.
Stay clear!
Move in...
Guys. on me. Let's move!
Move...
Move it!
Get over here. now!
Go...!
Move...! Tuck in...!
Kill the mortars...!
- Give me two...
- Alright. we need two men.
Let's go! Go...! Move!
Go...!
Go now. now!
Get ready. on my count!
Oh. my God.
So fucking close.
Push! Go! Again!
Western Forces have reached
the White House perimeter.
The President is now surrounded.
We have approached from Pennsylvania
Avenue where you can see that...
Just give me a minute.
We're gonna have to go again.
You getting good shit?
Lincoln Memorial.
You?
WF rappelling out of a chopper
on to the roof of
the fucking Pentagon.
There's really
only one shot though. huh?
You know he's in there?
They got intel from the generals
that surrendered yesterday.
The President's
right in that fucking building.
Fuck.
What do you hear
they're gonna do with him?
Kill.
No capture.
Whoever gets a fucking gun
to his head first.
Hey. Lee!
Don't beat me to the money shot. huh!
We got the beast.
Two suburbans. right outside.
The President's on the move.
Fuck yeah. He's bustin' out.
Vehicles coming through!
Beast...!
Another one!
President's vehicle
has been stopped
by Western Forces
as it attempted to escape.
He's not in there.
What?
Okay.
Let's go.
- Let's go. Jessie.
- What do you mean? What?
- Come on! Now!
- Fuck!
On me...
The reporter's moving out.
Don't shoot...!
This place is empty.
Stay the fuck out of our way.
On me.
Hold your fire!
I repeat. hold your fire!
I'm alone.
I'm unarmed.
Standing in the middle
of the press briefing room.
I'm Secret Service agent Joy Butler.
- Drop it.
- I'm unarmed.
I'm here to talk.
- Take it.
- Flood it.
I'm here to negotiate
the surrender of the President.
He's here.
Are you the WF?
Take a wild guess.
Can the President be entrusted
into your safe care?
Yes. ma'am.
We'll take real good care of him.
Just bring him out here.
We're not bringing him anywhere
until we have agreed terms.
You need to guarantee a safe passage
for the President.
And we need extraction
to a neutral territory.
We request Greenland or Alaska.
Nah. no terms. Bring him out here.
We gotta move. Sergeant.
Ma'am. the President is willing to...
Gunner! Point. check! Move in!
- Come on. get back!
- Contact one!
Just go. Go.
Out! Reloading!
- Get back!
Gun off!
Get him out! Out!
Crash! Cut the crash!
I'm out. Reloading...!
Right...
Crash it!
Go...!
Move in!
Wait...!
Chief. clear left!
Roger that!
Fire across. Bust across.
Check.
Forward.
Gunner. I'm moving across.
I need your lead as I fire.
Sergeant. you're going left.
Follow me. I'm going left.
You move when I move.
- Copy you!
- Guys. ready to move?
Ready. set
- move!
- Move it! Move!
Let's go!
Good?
Stay down.
Deacon. flare!
Move! You gotta move up!
Move...! Go! Move 'em out!
Moving!
Ready.
Break out...
Tuck in...!
- Out. I'm out! Reloading!
- Changing!
Prepping crash!
Wait!
I need a quote.
Don't let... don't let them kill me.
Yeah.
That'll do.
Do you want subtitles for any video?
-=[ ai.OpenSubtitles.com ]=-